<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name_long">Tethered Tent Triangulator</string>
    <string name="app_name_short">Tethered Tents</string>
    <string name="desc_clearing">Clearing Layout</string>

    <string name="desc_rotate">Rotate Tent or Platform</string>

    <string name="unit_meters">m</string>
    <string name="unit_meters_with_number">%1.1f m</string>
    <string name="desc_meters">Meters</string>

    <string name="unit_imperial">ft</string>
    <string name="unit_imperial_with_number">%1.0f ft</string>
    <string name="desc_imperial">Imperial (feet)</string>

    <string name="menu_default_tether">Reset Tether Points</string>
    <string name="menu_browser_tentsile">Tentsile Website</string>
    <string name="menu_browser_source_code">View the code!</string>
    <string name="menu_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="menu_switch_to_imperial">Use feet (ft)</string>
    <string name="menu_switch_to_meters">Use meters (m)</string>
    <string name="menu_increase_symbols">Increase symbols</string>
    <string name="menu_decrease_symbols">Decrease symbols</string>

    <string name="faq_accuracy_question">How accurately do I need to measure?</string>
    <string name="faq_accuracy_answer">The App itself is accurate to one decimeter or imperial
        foot.\n\nYou can use the app to get the measurements sufficiently close to then be able to
        align the tent according to the manufacturers instructions.</string>
    <string name="faq_all_at_once_question">What if my measurement goes off the screen?</string>
    <string name="faq_all_at_once_answer" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">Depending on the issue,
        you have a few options. You can...
        \n\n... drag the tether intersection point (if visible) to move all the anchors simultaneously.
        \n\n... tilt the device and modify anchors in that orientation.
        \n\n... reset the anchors using the menu option.
        \n\n... change the scale of the units using the slider.</string>
    <string name="faq_measurement_1_question">Do I need to know how thick the tree is?</string>
    <string name="faq_measurement_1_answer">You do not need to know where the center of the tree is.
        Instead, imagine a knot on the surface of each tree about where the tent tether would attach.
        Measure the distance from the imaginary knot on one tree to the imaginary knot on the next
        anchoring tree, etc.</string>
    <string name="faq_measurement_2_question">What am I measuring?</string>
    <string name="faq_measurement_2_answer">You are measuring the distances between approximate
        locations of the knots.</string>
    <string name="faq_missing_platform_question">Why is my tent not in the list?</string>
    <string name="faq_missing_platform_answer">Try dragging the list to see tents that are not in
        view. Otherwise, if it is a newer product, we may need to add it. In the meantime try using
        a tent or hammock with a similar \"footprint\" as yours.</string>
    <string name="faq_tools_question">What tools will I need?</string>
    <string name="faq_tools_answer">It helps to have a measuring tool handy, such as measuring tape
        or laser measuring tool. But, you could perform the measurements using consistently-spaced
        units, such as equally-spaced knots in a (low-stretch) string, sufficiently consistent
        paces, or even the straps that come with the tent. The point here is to measure using
        consistent units.</string>
    <string name="faq_symbol_orange_triangle_question">What does the orange triangle indicate?</string>
    <string name="faq_symbol_orange_triangle_answer">The orange triangle indicates that setup is
        possible, but involves a non-intuitive \"trick\".\n\nWrap the strap around the tree, as you
        usually do. Pass the ratchet, rather than the loose end of the strap, through the strap loop.
        Then tighten the strap as usual.</string>
    <string name="faq_symbol_yellow_triangle_question">What does the yellow triangle indicate?</string>
    <string name="faq_symbol_yellow_triangle_answer">The yellow triangle indicates that you will not
        have sufficient strap length to wrap around the tree according to recommendations.\n\nSetup
        using trees requires an extension or tree-protector strap for the tree with this symbol over
        it.</string>
    <string name="faq_symbol_red_x_question">What does the red X indicate?</string>
    <string name="faq_symbol_red_x_answer">The red X indicates that (ideal) setup is not possible.
        \n\nThe tree with the red X over it is too close.</string>
    <string name="faq_exiting_faq_page_question">How do I close this FAQ page?</string>
    <string name="faq_exiting_faq_page_answer">Press the back button to close this page.</string>
    <string name="faq_small_circles_on_tethers_question">What are the small circles shown on the tethers?</string>
    <string name="faq_small_circles_on_tethers_answer">The small circles are supposed to represent
        transition points, where the tethers change. For example, the tent corners, ratchets, and
        straps.</string>
    <string name="faq_notch_question">Why are some tents shown with an indentation?</string>
    <string name="faq_notch_answer">The indentation is there to clearly indicate the short edge of
        the tent. In a future release all tent edges will appear curved.</string>
    <string name="faq_curved_edges_question">Why are the tent edges shown as straight lines?</string>
    <string name="faq_curved_edges_answer">The edges are drawn straight for simplicity in drawing
        the tents and hammocks. In a future release all tent edges will appear curved.</string>
    <string name="faq_sight_indicator_question">Do I still need to use the tabs on the sides of my
        tent?</string>
    <string name="faq_sight_indicator_answer">That would be best. This app tries to get you close
        to the point where you can then align the tethers with the sight-indicator tabs on the sides
        of the non-equal-sided tents and hammocks.</string>

    <string name="url_source_code_android">https://github.com/munifrog/tentsile/tree/master/android/app/src</string>
    <string name="url_tentsile_website_main">https://www.tentsile.com/</string>
</resources>